And how are you brothers, today we are going to talk about
how you will be able to repay the EMI of your loan on your Xu Pop here,
if any loan is
running on your Xu Pop, be it a pay later loan or a
personal loan, any loan, and
you have to pay the EMI of your loan here, then
how will you have to make the payment,
come, I will show you live, for this
you do one thing, watch the video completely,
along with that you subscribe to our channel and
press the bell icon, now brothers,
after that, first of all you do one thing,
update your Xu app here and
open it, then your app will open here,
you do one thing, go to the bottom,
you will find a logo at the end,
tap here, then such a page will open in front of you,
whatever loan is running on your Xu Pop,
you will be able to check all the details from here,
if you have a pay later loan running on your Xu app, then
you do one thing, tap on Pay Later,
if you have a personal loan running on your account, then
you do one thing, tap on Personal Loan,
if you have
done Amazon2  If yes, then you will get the option of loan details here on
amazononline.in but if you want to check your loan
details then you will get the option of
loan details above, if you tap here then the
complete summary of your loan will open here,
how much loan amount is running on
your loan, how much interest is being charged on your loan, how much is
your EMI, how much is your tenor, how much did
you get in your bank account,
you will get the complete details of your loan here
but to make your EMI payment
you have to do one thing, back it up and
tap on Pay Now here again,
then the loan repayment
page will open in front of you, the amount of your EMI
remaining will come here, you
can see that this much EMI is remaining here, then
you will get the option to make the payment here
but if you want to close
your loan by paying the entire EMI of your loan at once, then
you will get the
option of pre close here next to it, by
tapping here you will be able to close the loan by paying the entire EMI of your loan at once,
but if we have to make only our EMI payment
then we will come down here and
we will get the option of Pay Now, you have to do one thing, tap  By
tapping on Now, the option of
making payment will open in front of you where you will
get three options for making payment,
first you will be able to make it through UPI, second you will be
able to make it through your debit card, third you will be able to make it through your net
banking, from where you have to
select and make the payment,
I will make the payment and show you the further
process, a few inches later,
now brothers you can see that I have made the
payment successfully here, now the
EMI of our loan has been paid here,
so brothers by doing this you will be
able to make the EMI payment of your loan here very easily on your X app,
I have shown you by doing it live, I hope
you must have known how to do it, if you
liked the video then like the video,
subscribe to the channel and press the bell icon